<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-01-02T15:15:55+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Joost Helfers</title><subtitle>Joost Helfers is a Creative Technologist working at the intersection of 3D, AI and emerging technology. His work is driven by a spatial approach, creating high-impact visuals and advanced technical workflows that help brands and designers communicate complex ideas. Combining his architectural and advanced 3D design background with startup experience, he builds innovative solutions that work.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On being a Generalist</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/02/on-being-a-generalist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On being a Generalist" /><published>2025-10-02T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2025-10-02T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/02/on-being-a-generalist</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/02/on-being-a-generalist.html"><![CDATA[<p>With my recent shift back to freelance work, I’ve thought a lot about my positioning, what I should call myself, and how to communicate my skills, experiences and the value I can bring to the table.</p>

<p>Probably I thought about it too much — now that I reflect on it. But this is what happens when chronic overthinking meets an uncertain experience overall.</p>

<p>I ended up deciding to call myself a “Creative Technologist” - this feels like a good term to describe my generalist skillset and approach to things. In recent years I’ve worked in so many different areas, from 3D visualization, to design engineering, building digital twins and last summer even being a car mechanic for a couple of weeks (I know how to change brake fluid in record time 😎). It would be weird to try to call myself something like AI Specialist or something, because quite frankly: I dove deep into the ComfyUI rabbit hole, but I am far from being a specialist. I have never trained custom weights or fine-tuned models. The most exciting thing I have done was training a mediocre LoRA (I’ll buy you a beer if you spot the image on my Labs feed).</p>

<p>Being a Generalist is fun I guess. And more than that, it’s useful — because projects rarely move in straight lines. Having someone who can adapt, connect different skills, and keep pushing until things work can be of immense value. That’s the mindset I try to bring into my freelance work: not just “doing a bit of everything”, but building the missing piece that makes the whole come together — and sometimes even adding something new that wasn’t there before.</p>

<p>On being a Generalist. Let’s go and build things.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a Generalist can feel daunting, but it has some really great advantages. This post explores my thoughts on embracing the Generalist mindset.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Souly &amp;amp; Boondawg - I got this feeling</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/09/10/souly-boondawg-music-video.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Souly &amp;amp; Boondawg - I got this feeling" /><published>2025-09-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2025-09-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/09/10/souly-boondawg-music-video</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/09/10/souly-boondawg-music-video.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h2>

<p>In collaboration with <a href="https://yyyyyyy.studio/">yyyyyyy.studio</a> as an AI Artist, I contributed to this hybrid production that seamlessly blends traditional greenscreen footage with generative AI environments. By leveraging advanced video-to-video models, we transposed the artists, Souly and Boondawg, into surreal, digitally constructed worlds, adding a distinct layer of visual narrative to the performance.</p>

<p style="font-size: 1.5rem; font-weight: 600; margin: 2rem 0;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j66rlYZQVeM" target="_blank">Watch the music video on YouTube ↗</a></p>

<div class="project-gallery-grid">
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-02.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-03.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-04.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-05.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-06.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-07.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
  <img src="/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-08.webp" alt="Scene from the music video" />
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="portfolio" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hybrid AI music video production transforming greenscreen footage into compelling visuals.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-02.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_Souly-Boondawg-igotthisfeelling/Souly-Boondawg_igotthisfeeling-02.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">INYO Mobility - Digital Twin Platform</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/05/04/inyo-digital-twin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="INYO Mobility - Digital Twin Platform" /><published>2025-05-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2025-05-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/05/04/inyo-digital-twin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2025/05/04/inyo-digital-twin.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h2>

<p>Developed a comprehensive digital twin platform for INYO Mobility’s electric vehicle development process. The platform combines real-time data visualization with interactive 3D models to optimize vehicle design and performance.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_3D-View.webp" alt="Digital Twin 3D View" />
<em>Interactive 3D view of the digital twin platform showing real-time vehicle data</em></p>

<h2 id="challenge">Challenge</h2>

<p>INYO Mobility needed a way to visualize and prototype vehicle designs without creating costly physical models. Traditional CAD workflows were slow and didn’t provide real-time performance insights.</p>

<h2 id="solution">Solution</h2>

<p>Created a digital twin system that provides:</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Real-time 3D Visualization</strong>: Interactive vehicle component models</li>
  <li><strong>Performance Simulation</strong>: Live testing of design modifications</li>
  <li><strong>Data Integration</strong>: Sensor data from test vehicles</li>
  <li><strong>Collaborative Tools</strong>: Multi-user design sessions</li>
</ul>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_Data-View-Chart.webp" alt="Data Visualization Charts" />
<em>Real-time data visualization showing vehicle performance metrics</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_Data-View-Chart2.webp" alt="Performance Analytics" />
<em>Advanced analytics dashboard for performance monitoring</em></p>

<h3 id="data-management--analytics">Data Management &amp; Analytics</h3>

<p>The platform includes comprehensive data management tools for tracking vehicle performance metrics and analyzing sensor data in real-time.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_Data-View-Table.webp" alt="Data Table View" />
<em>Comprehensive data table interface for detailed performance analysis</em></p>

<h2 id="technical-implementation">Technical Implementation</h2>

<p>The platform leverages modern web technologies:</p>
<ul>
  <li>WebGL-based 3D rendering for high performance</li>
  <li>Real-time data streaming and visualization</li>
  <li>Responsive design for cross-platform compatibility</li>
  <li>Modular architecture for future scalability</li>
</ul>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_Map-View.webp" alt="Geographic Data Visualization" />
<em>Geographic mapping interface for location-based vehicle tracking</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_Docker-Structure.webp" alt="System Architecture" />
<em>Technical system architecture and deployment structure</em></p>

<h2 id="results">Results</h2>

<p>Engineers reduced physical prototype iterations by 60%, accelerating the design process significantly while maintaining design quality and innovation standards.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="portfolio" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive 3D visualization solutions for vehicle design optimization | Full Stack development]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_3D-View.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Digital-Twin/Screenshot_3D-View.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Reviewing 2024</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/01/01/review-2024.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reviewing 2024" /><published>2025-01-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-01-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/01/01/review-2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/01/01/review-2024.html"><![CDATA[<p>2024 was a year of transformation for me — my first full year of working full-time, filled with challenges, growth, and plenty of lessons along the way. Time to look back on the past year while preparing for the coming one.</p>

<p>In January I moved to a small town near Munich and started my role as a Technical 3D artist at INYO and from then on the pace of work accelerated rapidly.</p>

<p>I learned a lot: refining my skills in 3D visualizations for real-world applications, navigating the dynamics of working at a start-up (it’s all about money and productive outcomes), collaborating successfully with multidisciplinary teams, and explaining my area of expertise to colleagues from different fields. I also gained insight into how cars and autonomous driving works, improved my task management skills, and even learned how to build a car (I have changed the break fluid on the INYO CAB so many times I’ve lost count). On top of that I mastered the art of packing light for long work trips and picked up so many other things along the way.</p>

<p>I really dove deep into so many areas and got to meet a lot of talented and inspiring people. This really motivated me and I am very grateful for opportunities I have at INYO (if you read this, thanks for the trust Marcus!!).</p>

<p>At the same time I realized that while working a lot, building and creating new things can be rewarding, but it’s also very important to not letting your identity be solely defined by your work. The long hours and seemingly never ending to-do list with tasks that are interesting but only partly igniting “passion” took a toll on my mental health.</p>

<p>I’ve already made some changes to address this: I transitioned to part-time freelance work, moved back to Berlin, and focused on passion projects outside of work. This includes designing furniture for my flat, setting up this website, and diving into web design and digital twins — areas I am eager to explore more deeply.</p>

<p>In 2025, I plan to deepen my expertise in digital twins, interactive design and all things 3D, while prioritizing personal projects that align with my values and goals. Balancing passion-driven work with sustainable and creative practices for my mental health is a key objective!</p>

<p>This year was interesting and I grew a lot. Let’s continue with this momentum into 2025 and focus on what sparks joy and truly matters!</p>

<p>Have a great year everyone.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look back at a transformative year. With experiences from startup life, hands-on 3D work to moving cities and rebalancing priorities. 2024 brought growth, learnings, and new beginnings as I plan a more intentional path into 2025.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DesignMorphine MSc Computational and Advanced Design - Project Arcadia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/designmorphine-msc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DesignMorphine MSc Computational and Advanced Design - Project Arcadia" /><published>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/designmorphine-msc</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/designmorphine-msc.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h2>

<p>Project Arcadia represents the culmination of my Master’s degree in Computational and Advanced Design. This project explores the intersection of parametric design, environmental responsiveness, and architectural form-finding through computational methods.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_01.webp" alt="Project Hero" />
<em>Main project visualization showcasing the parametric structure</em></p>

<h2 id="design-process">Design Process</h2>

<p>The project began with extensive research into responsive architectural systems and how computational tools can be used to create adaptive structures that respond to environmental conditions.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_02.webp" alt="Design Process 1" />
<em>Initial research and conceptual framework development</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_03.webp" alt="Design Process 2" />
<em>Computational methodology and parameter exploration</em></p>

<h3 id="computational-framework">Computational Framework</h3>

<p>The design framework was built using Grasshopper and custom Python components, allowing for real-time parameter adjustments and form optimization based on environmental data inputs.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_04.webp" alt="Computational Framework" />
<em>Computational design framework and parameter relationships</em></p>

<h2 id="development-phases">Development Phases</h2>

<p>The project evolved through multiple iterations, each refining the relationship between form, function, and environmental responsiveness.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_05.webp" alt="Development Phase 1" />
<em>First iteration exploring basic parametric relationships</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_06.webp" alt="Development Phase 2" />
<em>Refinement of environmental response mechanisms</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_07.webp" alt="Development Phase 3" />
<em>Advanced optimization and performance testing</em></p>

<h3 id="work-in-progress">Work in Progress</h3>

<div class="video-container">
  <iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c0c-HG-MEYA" title="Project Development Process" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>
<p><em>Development process and iterative design exploration</em></p>

<h2 id="final-design">Final Design</h2>

<p>The final design demonstrates a successful integration of computational design principles with architectural sensibility, creating a structure that is both formally compelling and environmentally responsive.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_08.webp" alt="Final Design" />
<em>Final design render showing the completed parametric structure</em></p>

<h3 id="project-video">Project Video</h3>

<div class="video-container">
  <iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1gLwwzydQ-c" title="DesignMorphine MSc Project" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>
<p><em>Final project presentation showcasing the complete design process and outcomes</em></p>

<h2 id="technical-implementation">Technical Implementation</h2>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Parametric Modeling</strong>: Grasshopper for visual programming</li>
  <li><strong>Environmental Analysis</strong>: Climate data integration for responsive behavior</li>
  <li><strong>Form Optimization</strong>: Python scripting for performance-based design</li>
  <li><strong>Visualization</strong>: High-quality rendering pipeline for presentation</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="key-learnings">Key Learnings</h2>

<p>This project taught me the importance of balancing computational complexity with design intent, and how parametric tools can be used not just for efficiency, but as a creative medium for architectural exploration.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="portfolio" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Final Project for my M. Sc. in Computational and Advanced Design]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_04.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_MSc-CAD/MSc-CAD_04.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">T-Cell AG - Explainer Videos</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/t-cell-explainer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="T-Cell AG - Explainer Videos" /><published>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/t-cell-explainer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/t-cell-explainer.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h2>

<p>Created a series of explainer videos for T-Cell AG to communicate the potential of hydrogen fuel cell technology for the energy transition. The videos focus on making complex scientific concepts accessible to a broad audience while maintaining technical accuracy.</p>

<h2 id="english-presentation-video">English Presentation Video</h2>

<video controls="" class="project-video">
  <source src="/assets/vids/T-Cell_Vorstellungsvideo_ENG_1440p.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
<p><em>Comprehensive presentation video explaining T-Cell’s hydrogen fuel cell technology and its applications</em></p>

<h2 id="german-mobile-version">German Mobile Version</h2>

<video controls="" class="project-video">
  <source src="/assets/vids/T-Cell_Mobil_DEU.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
<p><em>Mobile-optimized German version focusing on key benefits and applications</em></p>

<h2 id="project-goals">Project Goals</h2>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Educational Focus</strong>: Translate complex hydrogen technology into understandable concepts</li>
  <li><strong>Multi-Language Approach</strong>: Serve both English and German-speaking audiences</li>
  <li><strong>Mobile Optimization</strong>: Ensure accessibility across different devices and platforms</li>
  <li><strong>Scientific Accuracy</strong>: Maintain technical precision while improving accessibility</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="technical-approach">Technical Approach</h2>

<p>The videos combine scientific visualization with clear narrative structure to explain:</p>
<ul>
  <li>How hydrogen fuel cells work</li>
  <li>Environmental benefits of hydrogen technology</li>
  <li>Practical applications in the energy transition</li>
  <li>T-Cell AG’s role in advancing this technology</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="impact">Impact</h2>

<p>These explainer videos help T-Cell AG communicate their vision for hydrogen’s role in sustainable energy, making complex technology accessible to stakeholders, investors, and the general public interested in clean energy solutions.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="portfolio" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Series of videos for the T-Cell AG, explaining the hydrogen-fuel-cell technology and impact it can have for the energy transition.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_T-Cell/T-Cell_Hero.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_T-Cell/T-Cell_Hero.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">INYO Mobility - Various Visualizations</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/inyo-visualizations.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="INYO Mobility - Various Visualizations" /><published>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/inyo-visualizations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/portfolio/2023/05/01/inyo-visualizations.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h2>

<p>INYO Mobility is revolutionizing urban transportation with their innovative electric vehicle ecosystem. I created a comprehensive set of 3D visualizations and marketing materials to showcase their cutting-edge technology and design philosophy.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_00.webp" alt="INYO Hero Visualization" />
<em>Key hero visualization showcasing INYO’s electric vehicle design</em></p>

<h2 id="key-deliverables">Key Deliverables</h2>

<h3 id="3d-product-visualizations">3D Product Visualizations</h3>
<ul>
  <li>High-fidelity 3D models of INYO’s electric vehicles</li>
  <li>Photorealistic renderings for marketing campaigns</li>
  <li>Interactive 3D experiences for web presentations</li>
  <li>Technical visualization for product development</li>
</ul>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_01.webp" alt="Product Visualization 1" />
<em>Detailed product visualization highlighting vehicle design</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_02.webp" alt="Product Visualization 2" />
<em>Technical rendering showcasing engineering precision</em></p>

<h3 id="marketing-materials">Marketing Materials</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Digital assets for social media campaigns</li>
  <li>Print materials for trade shows and exhibitions</li>
  <li>Interactive presentations for investor meetings</li>
  <li>Brand-consistent visual identity across all materials</li>
</ul>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_03.webp" alt="Marketing Visualization" />
<em>Marketing visualization emphasizing the sleek design and innovation</em></p>

<h2 id="process--approach">Process &amp; Approach</h2>

<p>The project began with understanding INYO’s vision for sustainable urban mobility. I worked closely with their design team to ensure accuracy in technical details while maintaining the sleek, futuristic aesthetic that defines their brand.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_04.webp" alt="Design Process 1" />
<em>Initial design exploration and concept development</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_05.webp" alt="Design Process 2" />
<em>Refinement of visual style and technical accuracy</em></p>

<p><img src="/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_07.webp" alt="Design Process 3" />
<em>Final visualization polish and presentation preparation</em></p>

<h3 id="technical-implementation">Technical Implementation</h3>
<ul>
  <li><strong>3D Modeling</strong>: Created detailed vehicle models with accurate proportions and materials</li>
  <li><strong>Lighting &amp; Rendering</strong>: Developed lighting setups that emphasize the vehicles’ premium design</li>
  <li><strong>Post-Processing</strong>: Fine-tuned images for maximum impact across different media formats</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="results">Results</h2>

<p>The visualizations have been used across INYO’s marketing channels, helping them secure funding and partnerships. The materials effectively communicate the innovation and quality of their electric vehicle ecosystem to investors, customers, and media.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“The visualizations perfectly captured our vision and helped us communicate the potential of our technology to stakeholders.” - INYO Mobility Team</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="portfolio" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[3D visualizations and digital marketing materials for INYO Mobility's electric vehicle ecosystem]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_06.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/imgs/proj_INYO-Viz/INYO-Viz_06.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>